My wife says if i donated vy sumable time to charity
我妻子说，如果我把玩笑的时间都用在做慈善上，
I would have been quite a human being
我早就成为一个了不起的人了。
Ha ha ha
哈哈哈。
It's so thrilled to be able to say that this will be our sixtieth
我太激动了，这将是我们的第六十届，
And i'm proud of that
我为此感到骄傲。
There's only been six people in the history of the club
在俱乐部的历史上只有六个人做到过这件事，
And we met you at super bowl fifty one in houston
我们是在休斯顿的第五十一届超级碗上认识你的，
We did some research and said yo legitimate
我们做了一番核实，确认你是真的，
And we decided to make a shirt and induck
于是我们决定做一件T恤，把你纳入其中，
You went into the club and don
你就加入了俱乐部，唐，
That was a great thing for me
那对我来说意义重大。
I still have the pictures of all of us together that day
我还留着我们那天一起拍的照片。
The first super bowl started out like a college bowl game
第一届超级碗就像一场大学碗赛，
They had two college bands
有两支大学乐队演出，
They had a basket of pigeons they released
还有一篮子鸽子被放飞。
Now i'd cry from where we are today
和我们今天的超级碗相比，简直天壤之别。
You remember when prince were singing let it rain
你还记得王子在台上唱《Let It Rain》，
Let it rain and then start porn
唱着唱着天就真的下雨了，
It just ping with purple rain or something like that
就好像在和《Purple Rain》呼应。
Yes
是的。
come on
太棒了。
Did you ever come close to missing us
你有没有差点错过其中一届？
So oh my god
哦，天哪。
Suo thirty two in the morning on game day
比赛日当天凌晨两点半，
I pinned a little card on my shirt and said need one ticket
我在衬衣上别了张小纸条，写着"需要一张票"，
Have never missed a gentleman said i have three friends
从来没有一次缺席的我，一位绅士说他有三个朋友，
Whoever fourth ticket at first they didn't believe that i'd never missed a super bowl
不知道谁是第四张票的主人，他们起初不相信我从没错过一届超级碗。
So i said can i get my briefcase
我说，我去取我的公文包，
I can show you some photos
给你们看照片。
So i finally got ticket
我终于买到了票，
I sat with them and there was one of the benefits
和他们坐在一起，那还有个好处——
They all had a flask of chevis in their pocket . ha ha ha
他们口袋里都揣着一瓶芝华士。哈哈哈。
I've been saying for many years that it's over
我说了很多年，"快结束了"，
I had two or three health issues through the summer
这个夏天我经历了两三次健康问题，
And i thought that might prevent me for going
我以为这会让我没法去，
but then i could see my patriots were doing well
但后来我看到我的爱国者队成绩不错，
And i certainly wouldn't want to miss them
我肯定不会错过他们的比赛。
And unfortunately alliance haven't made it yet
遗憾的是，狮队至今还没进过超级碗。
Ha
哈。
I will always be a lion fan
我永远是狮队的球迷，
But i really enjoy every game
但我很享受每一场比赛，
Even if my team wasn't in or not
不管我的队伍在不在场。
And don , i hope you go another year
唐，我希望你再去一年。
We'll see it's pretty challenging
我们拭目以待，这颇具挑战性，
We've lost three members
我们已经失去了三位成员，
but we're pulling it off for the last time
但我们正在为最后一次竭尽全力，
And i think the people in the club are just as important as of the game
我觉得俱乐部里的这些人，和比赛本身一样重要。
Hey man
伙计，
Well don you a great human being
唐，你真是个好人。
Being with you guys is something i treasure for the rest of my life
能和你们在一起，是我余生最珍贵的财富。
I've been lucky to have met you
能认识你，我真的很幸运。